斯科特：星舰日志，星历5710.5
SCOTT: Ship's log, stardate 5710.5.
斯科特少校报道
Lieutenant Commander Scott reporting.
在探索外部象限时，企业号收到了求救信号
While exploring an outer quadrant, the Enterprise received distress calls
来自斯卡罗斯星球上一座无人居住的美丽城市
from an uninhabited, incredibly beautiful city on the planet of Scalos.
柯克舰长和一个登陆小队已经传送下去了
Captain Kirk and a landing party have beamed down.
柯克：你的传感器读数是什么？
KIRK: What do your sensors read?
它有显示，但我不知道是什么
They register something, but I can't figure out what.
- 具体说明  - 我无法定位
- Specify. - I can't get a fix on it.
传感器无法准确定位
Sensors don't pinpoint a location.
- 我要检查电路  - 你试试
- I'm about to check circuits. - You do that.
乌乎拉，求救信号的位置
Uhura, does the location of the distress call
与这个区域完全对应吗？
correspond with this area exactly?
是的，先生，我仍在接收可视通讯
Yes, sir. I'm still receiving visual contact.
我可以看到他们，但我看不到你
I can see them but I can't see you.
- 是同一个区域吗？  - 坐标一致，舰长
- Is it the same area? - Coordinates correspond, Captain.
除了登陆小队，这里没有任何人，没有斯卡罗斯人
Apart from the landing party, there is no one here. There are no Scalosians.
求救信号很强，舰长
The distress call is very strong, Captain.
他们正在恳求援助
They are pleading for assistance.
检查电路是否有故障，通话完毕
Check circuits for malfunctions. Kirk out.
这是一个荒芜的世界，几乎没有任何植被，没有动物
This is a barren world. There's hardly any vegetation, no animal life.
我们应该有一些解释
We should have some explanation.
但是有昆虫
But there is an insect life.
- 我的三录仪没显示  - 我听到了
- My tricorder doesn't register it. - Registers in my ears.
- 没有什么？  - 显然是一个高级文明
- Nothing? - Evidently a civilization of high order.
工业规模排名第7
Rating number 7 on the industrial scale,
根据绘画，是人形生物
humanoid according to the paintings.
大量文献，我将翻译和处理
An abundance of literature, which I shall have translated and processed.
某些建筑物有最近入住的证据
Certain structures hold evidence of recent occupancy,
而其他建筑物则早已废弃
while others are long abandoned.
- 没有存在生命的迹象？  - 读数显示有生命形式
- No sign of present life? - Readings indicate life-forms.
但不寻常且断断续续
But of an unusual and intermittent nature.
它们没有可辨别的形式或位置
They have no discernible form or location.
一个令人费解的现象，我需要进一步研究
A puzzling phenomenon. I shall have to study it further.
有东西刚刚在这里，我们在屏幕上看到了他们
Something was here. We saw them on the screen.
- 发生了什么？  - 目前未知
- What happened? - Unknown at present.
史波克先生，我希望您使用船上所有可用的仪器进行调查
Mr. Spock, I want you to run a survey, using all ship's available instruments.
康普顿！
Compton!
- 发生了什么？  - 我正看着他…
- What happened? - I was looking at him...
我正看着他，然后他就消失了
I was looking right at him. Then he just wasn't there.
柯克：宇宙，最后的边疆
KIRK: Space, the final frontier.
这些是星舰企业号的航程
These are the voyages of the starship Enterprise.
它的五年任务：探索未知的新世界
Its five-year mission: To explore strange new worlds,
寻找新生命和新文明
to seek out new life and new civilizations,
勇踏前人未至之境
to boldly go where no man has gone before.
开始重播求救信号
Start a replay of the distress call.
传送装置能否正常工作？
Is the transporter functioning?
- 是的，史波克在哪里？  - 在医务室
- Aye. Where's Spock? - In Sickbay.
麦考伊医生正在检查登陆小队
Dr. McCoy is running a check on the landing party.
- 怎么了？  - 故障，长官
- What is it? - Malfunction, sir.
- 苏鲁先生，我想…  - 舰长，它自动纠正了
- Mr. Sulu, I would like... - Captain, it corrected itself.
机库甲板上有麻烦，控制器被冻结
There's trouble on the hangar deck. The controls are frozen.
- 是否指派了维修人员？  - 是的，长官
- Are repair crews assigned? - Yes, sir.
- 磁带准备好了，长官  - 播放
- The tape is ready, sir. - Play it.
致所有在斯卡罗斯星球范围内经过的太空旅行者
To any and all space travelers passing within range of the planet Scalos.
我向您发出紧急求助请求
I send you an urgent appeal for help.
我们是曾经繁荣的文明中最后幸存的成员
We are the last surviving members of what was once a thriving civilization.
我们在这个地区避难
We have taken shelter in this area.
我们无法解释发生了什么
We have no explanation for what has been happening.
我们现在有五个人，我们曾经是一个拥有90万人口的国家
Our number is now five. We were once a nation of 900,000.
停
Freeze it.
我假设这个求救信号是预先录制的
I assume this distress call was pre-recorded.
我们收到的是一条延迟的录音消息
What we received was a delayed taped message.
这就是为什么我们收到它
That's why we received it
而我们的传感器只收到登陆小队
while our sensors picked up only the landing party.
当我们传送下去时，我们找不到那些人
When we beamed down, we couldn't find those people.
他们原来在那里，现在不在了，但康普顿不是
They were there, now they're not. Nor is Compton.
似乎是某种力量或媒介
It would seem that some force or agent
我们的仪器只能部分识别
only partly discernible to our instruments
导致了这个状况
may have been responsible.
当我们继续调查时，我希望这艘船处于待命状态
I want the ship on standby alert while we continue the investigation.
现在我有读数表明护盾不起作用
Now I have readings that the deflectors are inoperative.
斯科提，帮忙
Scotty, assist.
自从我们传送上来后，就出现了故障
Ever since we beamed up we've had malfunctions.
我要一份调查和说明报告
I want an investigation and an explanation.
麦考伊呼叫柯克舰长，请求舰长到场
McCoy to Captain Kirk. Captain's presence is requested.
不能等等吗？
Can't it wait?
你的命令，吉姆，你是最后一个
Your orders, Jim. You're the last one.
- 到目前为止你怎么看？  - 我们可以在这里讨论吗？
- What do you read so far? - Can we discuss it here?
我来了，史波克先生，你指挥
On my way. Mr. Spock, you have the conn.
- 怎么了？  - 告诉他
- What is it? - Tell him.
有人打开了所有的医疗用品柜
Somebody's opened all the medical supply cabinets.
- 有什么丢了吗？  - 没有
- Anything missing? - No.
就好像有人拿起所有东西研究了一番
It's just as though someone had picked up everything.
- 躺下  - 这与其他干扰相吻合
- Lie down. - That fits with other disturbances.
老骨头，其他人的读数是什么？
Bones, what did your readings show up on the other men?
一切正常
All normal.
发生在康普顿身上的事情对其他人都没有影响
Whatever happened to Compton had no effect on anyone else.
他们中有人报告在传送后有什么不寻常的经历吗？
Any of them report any unusual experience since beaming up?
不，没有人提到
No, there's no mention of it.
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
- 我还没说完  - 稍等
- I'm not finished yet. - Hold on.
骨头，会不会有什么东西让我产生幻觉？
Bones, could something be making me hallucinate?
你是什​​么意思？
What do you mean?
之前有过两次，什么东西触碰了我，但周围什么都没有
Twice before, something touched me, and there was nothing there.
刚刚又发生了
And it's just happened again.
是我的想象吗？
Could I be imagining it?
身体上，你没有任何问题
Physically, there's nothing wrong with you.
但是我是不是出现幻觉了？
But am I hallucinating?
我猜不是
I'd say no.
那我们一定传送了什么东西上船
Then we did beam something aboard.
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
有什么东西侵入了这艘船
Something has invaded the ship.
柯克呼叫史波克，请回答，史波克，请回答
Kirk to Spock, come in. Spock, come in.
史波克[通过对讲机]：我有一个生命支持系统的读数
SPOCK [OVER INTERCOM]: I have a reading from life-support.
史波克，我听不见你说话
Spock, I can't hear you.
检查你的电路
Check your circuits.
乌乎拉[通过对讲机]：对讲系统出现故障
UHURA [OVER INTERCOM]: Intercom system is breaking down.
全船命令，使用通讯器代替对讲机
Ship-wide order. Use communicators instead of intercom.
向所有船员发放相位枪
Issue phasers to all crew members.
- 史波克？  - 我有一个生命支持的读数
- Spock? - I have a reading from life-support.
- 外来物质被引入  - 立刻来见我
- Alien substances being introduced. - Meet me on the double.
- 史波克？  - 这是一个陌生的力场
- Spock? - It is an unfamiliar force field.
有一个和星球表面类似的外星人存在
There's an alien presence similar to that on the planet's surface.
- 但它没有确切的位置  - 相位枪击晕模式，搜索这个区域
- But it has no exact location. - Phasers on stun. Sweep the area.
看来他们打算只让我们两个人进去
It seems that they intend to allow only the two of us to enter.
我建议谨慎行事
I should advise caution.
它是什么？
What is it?
不知道，舰长，但它显然是外星来源的装置
Unknown, Captain, but it is evidently a device of alien origin.
接入了生命支持系统，企图影响它
Hooked into the life-support. Designed to affect it.
生命支持系统仍在运作，我猜安装还没有完成
Life-support is still operating. I'd say that the installation is incomplete.
断开它
Disconnect it.
[嘶嘶响]
[FIZZ]
破坏它
Destroy it.
有什么东西把我推了回去，他们在这里
Something shoved me back. They're in here.
你！你在我的船上做什么？
You! What are you doing on my ship?
现身！
Show yourselves!
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
似乎我们可以看着，舰长，但仅此而已
It seems that we may look at it, Captain, but that is all.
- 展示实力  - 他们认为我们无法阻止他们
- A show of strength. - They think we cannot stop them,
他们想让我们知道他们能对我们做什么
and they wish to impress upon us what they can do to us.
您的读数录入计算机了吗？
Have your readings been fed into the computer?
- 是的  - 读出来
- Affirmative. - Read out.
计算机，分析并回复，我们被入侵了吗？
Computer, analyze and reply. Have we been invaded?
- 计算机：是的  - 敌军描述
- COMPUTER: Affirmative. - Description of enemy forces.
- 数据不足  - 敌军数量
- Data insufficient. - Number of enemy forces.
- 数据不足  - 入侵的目的
- Data insufficient. - Purpose of the invasion.
直接目的：夺取和控制
Immediate purpose: seizure and control
星舰企业号和船员
of starship Enterprise and crew.
数据不足以确定最终目的
Data insufficient for determination of end purpose.
这和康普顿的失踪有关系吗？
Is there a connection between this and Compton's disappearance?
- 数据不足  - 我们有能力抵抗吗？
- Data insufficient. - Are we capable of resisting?
- 没有  - 你的建议？
- Negative. - Your recommendations?
如果无法抵抗，可以谈判条件
If incapable of resistance, negotiate for terms.
- 我们不会谈判，你同意吗？  - 是的
- We will not negotiate. You concur? - Aye.
你的建议，舰长？
Your recommendations, Captain?
在喝咖啡还是电路也损坏了？
Is that coffee available or have those circuits been damaged as well?
我的建议？让他们采取下一步行动
My recommendation? Make them take the next step.
史波克？
Spock?
舰长
Captain.
介意解释一下吗…
Would you mind explaining...
- 你是谁？  - 迪拉，敌人
- Who are you? - Deela. The enemy.
- 你是敌人？  - 是的
- You're the enemy? - Yes.
你亲自传送我上船的
You beamed me aboard yourself.
漫长得出奇的过程，但我搞定了
Ridiculously long process, but I've taken care of it.
- 你对我的人做了什么？  - 没有什么
- What have you done with my men? - Nothing.
史波克先生？
Mr. Spock?
斯科提？
Scotty?
- 这是没什么？  - 他们没有任何问题
- This is nothing? - There's nothing wrong with them.
他们一如往常
They are just as they have always been.
不一样的是你
It's you who are different.
上尉
Lieutenant.
苏鲁
Sulu.
这是没问题？
This is nothing?
在他们的耳朵里，你听起来像一只昆虫
To their ears you sound like an insect.
这就是你的描述，舰长，坦率地说，很准确
That's your description, Captain. Accurate, if unflattering.
真的，他们没有任何问题
Really, there is nothing wrong with them.
- 你做了什么？  - 改变了你
- What have you done? - Changed you.
你现在和我一样
You are like me now.
由于加速，你的船员无法看到你或我们中的任何人
Your crew cannot see you or any of us because of the acceleration.
我们眨眼之间就移动了
We move in the wink of an eye.
对此有科学的解释
There is a scientific explanation for it.
但真正重要的是你能看到我
But all that really matters is that you can see me,
和我说话
and talk to me,
而且…我们可以从那里继续
and... we can go on from there.
- 为什么？  - 因为我喜欢你，你没有猜到吗？
- Why? - Because I like you. Didn't you guess?
还是说你习惯被隐形的女人亲吻？
Or are you used to being kissed by invisible women?
迪拉
Deela.
这就是你破坏我的​​飞船的原因吗？
Is this why you sabotaged my ship?
它没有被破坏，我们不得不做出一些改变来调整它
It has not been sabotaged. We had to make some changes to adjust it to us.
- 你说“我们”  - 是的，当然
- You said "we". - Yes, of course.
我的首席科学家和他的团队
My chief scientist and his crew.
我是他们的女王
I am their queen.
你将成为他们的国王
You are going to be their king.
您将享受生活在斯卡罗斯的乐趣
You'll enjoy living on Scalos.
我的飞船？我的船员怎么办？
What about my ship? My crew?
一会儿他们就会意识到你消失了
In a few of their moments, they will realize that you've vanished.
他们会找你，但他们不会找到你
They will look for you, but they will not find you.
你的速度超出了他们的视觉能力
You're accelerated beyond their power to see.
所以他们会在没有你的情况下继续前进
So they'll go on without you.
不要那么固执，你永远不能回到他们身边
Don't be so stubborn. You cannot go back to them, ever.
前景有那么可怕吗？
Is it so dreadful a prospect?
这不会杀死你，但眩晕效果不是很愉快
This won't kill you, but the stun effect is not very pleasant.
[笑]但这行不通
[LAUGHS] But that won't work.
你继续，试试
You go ahead. Try.
直接指着我
Point it right at me.
对于这种粗糙的武器，我的反应太快了
My reactions are much too fast for such a crude weapon.
而且我也很擅长自卫
And I am quite good at self-defense, too.
这个也可以设定为击晕和摧毁
This can be set for stun and destroy, too.
请接受已经发生的事情
Please. Accept what has happened.
你无法改变它
There is nothing you can do to change it.
如果我同意和你走，你会让飞船恢复正常
If I agree to go with you, will you set this ship to rights,
拿走生命支持系统中的那个装置吗？
take out that device in life-support?
别傻了，过一阵你就感觉好多了
Don't be silly. You'll feel better about it all in a while.
总是这样，他们一开始很不高兴
It always happens this way. They are very upset at first.
然后慢慢平息，然后…学会喜欢它
Then it wears off, then they... they learn to like it.
你也会的
You will, too.
他正在向你走来，对他温柔点
He's on his way to you. Be gentle with him.
舰长…柯克舰长！他走了
Captain... Captain Kirk! He's gone.
- 你看到发生了什么吗？  - 他喝了咖啡，放下杯子
- Did you see what happened? - He drank his coffee and set it down.
- 然后他消失了  - 苏鲁先生，你确认了吗？
- And then he vanished. - Mr. Sulu, do you verify?
是的，他在那里，然后突然他就不在那里了
Yes. He was there, then all of a sudden he wasn't there.
- 你成功了  - 康普顿，他们加速了你
- You've made it. - Compton. They've accelerated you.
他们把什么东西接入了生命支持系统
They've hooked something into life-support.
- 我们必须把它弄走  - 禁止进入
- We must get rid of it. - Entry is forbidden.
- 谁的命令？  - 指挥官
- By whose order? - The commander.
我是你的指挥官，我命令你让我进去
I am your commander. I order you to let me in.
- 抱歉，你已经不是了  - 谁是？迪拉？
- I'm sorry. You are no longer. - Who is? Deela?
你替她工作吗？
Is that who you're working for?
一开始我拒绝了，但后来我控制不住自己
At first I refused, but then I couldn't help myself.
我遇见了这个女孩，她是他们中的一员，我从来不知道有像她这样的人
I met this girl. She's one of them. I've never known anyone like her.
我给他们展示了这艘船的操作
I showed them the operation of the ship.
舰桥控制，生命支持系统
Bridge controls, life-support.
她解释说他们想知道
She explained that they wanted to know.
一开始我不明白，但现在我明白了，你也会明白的，长官
I didn't understand at first, but I do now. So will you, sir.
好吧，康普顿
All right, Compton.
击晕
Stun.
你被命令阻止他，你为什么不服从？
You were ordered to stop him. Why did you disobey?
我试图阻止他
I tried to stop him.
- 你伤害了他  - 他必须被制服
- You hurt him. - He had to be subdued.
他是我的…舰长
He was my... captain.
细胞损伤
Cell damage.
另一个对你很安全
Another will be secured for you.
我得到一个与星球上相似的读数
I'm getting a reading similar to that on the planet.
- 苏鲁先生，你喝咖啡了吗？  - 是的
- Mr. Sulu, did you drink your coffee? - Yes.
- 其他人呢？  - 我喝了一些
- Did anyone else? - I had some.
- 我可以吗？  - 是咖啡吗？我们也会消失吗？
- May I? - Was it the coffee? Will we go, too?
在分析完这些之前我不会知道
I won't know until these have been analyzed.
- 那就太迟了  - 记住舰长的话
- Then it'll be too late. - Recall the captain's words.
“让他们采取下一步行动”，他们已经采取了
"Make them take the next step." They have taken it.
我们必须确定有效的对策
And we must determine effective counter measures.
斯科特先生，你来指挥，我去实验室
Mr. Scott, you have the conn. I shall be in the lab.
我讨厌他们受损后的发生的事情
I hate what happens when they're damaged.
你必须控制你的脾气
You must control your temper.
我不希望这种情况发生在这个人身上
I do not want that to happen to this one.
如果他们是一个如此顽固的物种，也许他们能坚持更长时间
If they are so stubborn a species, perhaps they will last longer.
- 可能吧  - 但愿如此
- It may be. - I hope so.
他们都这么快就走了，我想长期留着这个，他很漂亮
They all go so soon. I want to keep this one a long time. He's pretty.
- 他是低等的，迪拉  - 我不这么认为
- He is inferior, Deela. - I don't think so.
你不能让自己迷恋上他
You cannot allow yourself to feel attached.
我可以随心所欲
I can allow myself anything I want.
雷尔，别这样，我嫉妒你的所作所为吗？
Rael, don't be like that. Am I jealous of what you do?
- 我履行我的职责  - 我也是
- I do my duty. - So do I.
有时我允许自己享受它
And sometimes I allow myself to enjoy it.
你好
Hello.
那个设备在我的船上做什么？
What is that device doing on my ship?
迪拉会解释的
Deela will explain it.
我会告诉你一切，你会同意的
I will tell you everything, and you'll approve of it.
同意？我们是你的俘虏
Approve of it? We're your prisoners.
并不是，你可以自由地去任何你想去的地方
Hardly. You're free to go anywhere you want to.
去吧，舰长
Go ahead, Captain.
它尚未完全连接，但它处于运行状态
It is not yet completely linked, but it is in operating order.
如果你愿意，研究它，我建议你不要碰它
Study it if you wish. I suggest that you do not touch it.
他告诉你不要碰它，看看你的手，几乎被冻僵了
He told you not to touch it. Look at your hands. They're almost frozen.
会好的
It will pass.
它有自己的自卫机制
It has its own self-defense mechanism.
你应该听我的
You should have heeded me.
在你与康普顿的斗争中，他的一些细胞被损坏了
In your struggle with Compton, some of his cells were damaged.
新加速人的对细胞损伤很敏感
Those newly accelerated are sensitive to cell damage.
他们会很快衰老并死亡
They age very rapidly and die.
- 他还那么年轻  - 曾经
- He was so young. - Was.
- 这就是你为我们计划的？  - 我们都会死，即使在斯卡罗斯
- This is what you have planned for us? - We all die. Even on Scalos.
你为什么要骗他？
Why did you lie to him?
- 他没有伤害那个人，是你  - 也许他现在会少一些暴力
- He did not damage that one. You did. - Perhaps he will be less violent now.
- 为什么让他感觉更糟？  - 你为什么在乎？
- Why make him feel worse? - Why do you care?
雷尔，他不是我们中的一员，他只是暂时的
Rael, he's not one of us. He's temporary.
他去了实验室
He's gone to the laboratory.
他正在尝试与瓦肯人交流
He's trying to communicate with the Vulcan.
他的物种能够产生很多感情
His species is capable of much affection.
- 我已经注意到了  - 我想知道他们是否会向我们展示它
- I have noted that. - I wonder if they'll show it to us.
哦，雷尔，别生闷气了
Oh, Rael, stop sulking.
接受现实吧，我们一辈子都得接受现实
Accept it. We've had to accept it all our lives.
不要让事情变得更糟
Don't make it worse.
回去工作
Go back to work.
柯克呼叫史波克
Kirk to Spock.
我已将所有可查明的事实输入计算机库
I have fed all the ascertainable facts into the computer banks.
去吧，你不会有任何成就
Go ahead. You won't accomplish anything,
但它可能具有历史价值
but it may be historically valuable.
超加速是关键
Hyperacceleration is the key.
我只数到了五，但他们已经接管了这艘船
I have counted only five but they have taken over the ship,
由于这种加速，我们处于他们的控制之下
and we are under their control due to this acceleration.
他们能够加速其他人达到他们的级别
They are able to speed others up to their level,
正如康普顿和我
as they did Compton and me.
据推测，这是一种奴役方式
Presumably, this is enslavement.
那些被如此对待的人
Those so treated
存在于这种加速的级别
exist at this accelerated level,
最终变得…温顺
becoming... docile eventually.
- 但是当…  - 受伤时
- But when... - Damaged.
…受伤时，他们衰老得非常快
...damaged, they age incredibly fast,
仿佛加速的生活…
as though accelerated living...
- 耗尽了他们  - …耗尽了他们
- Burns them out. - ...burns them out.
康普顿被耗尽了
Compton was burned out.
连接到生命支持系统的装置
The device attached to the life-support systems
产生一种极度的，麻木的寒冷
produces an extreme, numbing cold.
我认为他们正在把企业号变成
I believe they are turning the Enterprise
一个巨大的深度冷冻的…
into a gigantic deep-freeze...
目的只有斯卡洛人知道
for purposes only the Scalosians know.
相当正确
Quite correct.
该装置有一个防护罩，不允许任何物理接触
The unit has a protective shield which does not allow any physical contact.
我不知道如何摧毁它，但摧毁它势在必行
I don't know how to destroy it, but its destruction is imperative.
装置将被激活，当他们听到这些时
The unit will be activated. By the time they hear this,
已经太晚了
it will be too late.
你有非凡的推理能力，你说得很对
You have remarkable reasoning powers. You were quite right.
- 你为什么这么做？  - 你真的想知道吗？
- Why are you doing this? - Do you really want to know?
很快这对你就不重要了，你会很高兴的
Soon it won't matter to you at all. You'll be happy about it.
- 就像康普顿一样  - 我想知道
- Just as Compton was. - I want to know.
你太固执了，很明显，我们这样做是因为我们必须这样做
You are so stubborn. It's obvious that we're doing it because we must.
很久以前--在我们的历史中--我们曾经像你们一样
A long time ago -- it is in our history -- we used to be like you.
然后我们的国家几乎被火山爆发摧毁了
Then our country was almost destroyed by volcanic eruptions.
水被污染了，辐射被释放了
The water was polluted. Radiation was released.
那改变了我们，它加速了我们
That changed us. It accelerated us.
孩子们死了，大多数女人都不能再有孩子了
Children died. Most of the women could not have any more.
因为所有的男人都变得不育了
All of our men had become sterile.
所以我们不得不与其他人交配
So we had to mate outside our own people.
每当有宇宙飞船驶过时，我们都会请求帮助
Whenever a spaceship came by, we called for help.
但是加速他们耗尽了他们
But accelerating them burned them out.
你明白吗？我需要解释每个细节吗？
Don't you see? Do I have to go into every detail?
我们要带你一起下来
We are going to take you down with us.
也许再带一两个你的船员
Perhaps one or two others of your crew.
我们必须这么做
We have to.
我们会善待你的，我不会伤害你的，我确实喜欢你
We'll be kind to you. I wouldn't hurt you. I do like you.
我的船员呢？
What about my crew?
他们将停留在假死状态
They will stay in suspended animation.
它不会对他们造成任何伤害
It will do them no harm.
我们正在保存他们以备不时之需
We are saving them for when we need them.
你不会永远活下去，你知道的，舰长
You will not last for ever. You know that, Captain.
我们有生存的权利
We have the right to survive.
- 不是通过杀死他人  - 你也会这样做
- Not by killing others. - You would do the same.
当你知道有麻烦时，你就冲入了生命支持系统
You charged into life-support when you knew there was trouble.
- 你会杀了我的人民  - 你入侵了我的船
- You would have killed my people. - You invaded my ship.
- 没有区别！  - 有！
- There is no difference! - There is!
你们的问题…在你们自身
Your trouble... is in you.
不是我们想这样，我们正在以我们知道的唯一方式处理它
We did not ask for it. We are handling it the only way we know how.
我们的父母和他们的父母所做的方式
The way our parents and their parents did.
他们解决了什么问题吗？你们有没有试过其他方式？
Did they solve anything? Have you tried any other way?
迪拉，让你的科学家摧毁那个单位
Deela, have your scientists destroy that unit.
我向你保证，我们将使用我们所拥有的一切技能来帮助你
I promise you, we'll use every skill we have to help you.
我们会把你们带到另一个星球，我们会召集最聪明的人来提供帮助
We'll move you to another planet. We'll call in the most brilliant minds to help.
- 我们会的…  - 我们尝试过其他方法
- We'll do... - We have tried other ways.
我们已经试过转变到你们的级别
We have tried to make the transition to your level.
我们中的一些人，就是这样，那些作出尝试的人都死了
Some of us, that is. Those who made the attempt died.
我们被困住了，舰长，就像你现在被困住了一样
We are trapped, Captain, just as you are trapped now.
我对要发生的事情感到抱歉，但我无法改变它
I'm sorry for what's going to happen, but I cannot change it.
你不能改变我
You cannot change me.
雷尔[通过无线电]：去传送室，迪拉
RAEL [OVER RADIO]: Go to the transporter room, Deela.
给我发信号并传送下去
Signal me and beam down.
- 和舰长？  - 是的
- With the captain? - Yes.
我会激活我们的装置并跟上你
I'll activate our unit and follow you.
我给大家留出足够的时间下船
I'm allowing enough time for all of us to get off the ship.
- 请不要拖延  - 是什么让你认为我会拖延？
- Please don't delay. - What makes you think I would?
- 舰长逃走了  - 去追他！
- The captain's gone. - Go after him!
毫无疑问，我想让你看看这个
There's no question about it. I want you to take a look at this.
它存在于舰长的咖啡和斯卡罗斯的水中
It's in the captain's coffee and the Scalosian water.
其他杯子里没有任何痕迹
There's no trace in the other cups.
- 你为什么跑？  - 我惊慌失措
- Why did you run? - I panicked.
- 我不相信  - 我想离开
- I don't believe that. - I'd like to leave.
你可以启动了
You can activate.
雷尔[通过无线电]：立刻把他传送下去
RAEL [OVER RADIO]: Beam him down at once.
舰长
Captain.
- 你对传送装置做了什么？  - 它之前可以用
- What did you do to the transporter? - It was working before.
再试一次
Try it again.
- 传送装置不工作  - 他对它做了什么？
- The transporter isn't working. - What did he do to it?
没有什么，他没有那个时间
Nothing. He didn't have time.
一定是…你们怎么说的？故障
It must be a... what do you call it? A malfunction.
你最好不要激活这个装置
You'd better not activate the unit yet.
你有什么看法，舰长？
What would you say it is, Captain?
技术人员报告说断电了，一定是这样
The technicians reported a loss of power. That must be it.
- 舰长说…  - 我听到了，我不相信他
- The captain says... - I heard him. I don't believe him.
检查所有可能的原因
Check into all possible causes.
如果我本性多疑，舰长
If I had a suspicious nature, Captain,
我会说你破坏了传送装置以争取时间
I would say that you sabotaged the transporter to buy time.
是的，当然
Yes, of course.
我很高兴我们都是无辜的，我鄙视狡猾的人，你呢？
I'm glad we're both innocents. I despise devious people, don't you?
我自己也相信诚实的关系
I believe in honest relationships myself.
护士，确定我们是否可以找到反作用剂
Nurse, determine whether we can find counter agents.
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
医生，你刚才…
Doctor, did you just...
自从我们传送到斯卡罗斯，我就一直听到这种嗡嗡声
I've been hearing that whine ever since we beamed down to Scalos.
我知道它是什么，我们从斯卡罗斯带来了它
I know what it is. We brought it with us from Scalos.
对不起，医生，我应该在舰桥上
Excuse me, Doctor. I shall be on the bridge.
你的宿舍很像你--简朴而高效
Your quarters are quite like you -- austere and efficient,
有自己的格调，英俊
and in their own way, handsome.
一个房间能反映它的居住者
A room should reflect its occupant.
的确，我可以梳洗一下吗？
Absolutely. May I freshen up?
这匆匆忙忙的事情让我的头发都乱了
All this rushing about has left me windblown.
我很高兴看到你让自己舒服点
I'm glad to see you allow yourself some comforts.
你结婚了吗，舰长？
Are you married, Captain?
没有家庭？没有牵挂？
No family? No attachments?
我知道，你嫁给了你的事业，你从不看其他女人
I know. You're married to your career and you never look at another woman.
嗯，如果她足够漂亮，我会看的
Well, if she's pretty enough, I'll look.
我想知道你什么时候会对我说些好话
I wondered when you'd say something nice to me.
我现在更好看了吗？
Am I more presentable now?
一点点
A bit.
在你看不见我的时候吻你是件很愉快的事
It was quite delightful kissing you when you couldn't see me.
- 但是现在…  - 但是现在…
- But now... - But now...
不，我不会允许你拿走它的
No. I wouldn't allow you to take that,
无论我们多么信任对方
no matter how much we trust each other.
但如果你没有尝试，我会失望的
But I would have been disappointed if you hadn't tried.
我是不是…太粗鲁了？
Was I... too crude?
只是别再试了，你太容易受到皮肤损伤了
Just don't try it again. You're far too vulnerable to skin damage.
我只要…抓一下你
All I have to do is... scratch you.
是的，我知道
Yes, I know.
我们之间的区别在于
The difference between us is that
你会认同我们的思维方式
you will come around to our way of thinking.
但早一点比晚一点好
But it's better sooner than later.
在我的显示器上重播斯卡罗斯人的求救信号
Replay the Scalosian distress call on my viewer.
致所有在斯卡罗斯星球范围内经过的太空旅行者
To any and all space travelers passing within range of the planet Scalos.
我向您发出紧急求助请求
I send you an urgent appeal for help.
我们是曾经繁荣的文明中最后幸存的成员
We are the last surviving members of what was once a thriving civilization.
- 康普顿？  - 发生了什么？
- Compton? - What happened?
我正看着他，我正看着他，然后他就消失了
I was looking at him. I was looking right at him then he just wasn't there.
我们在这个地区避难
We have taken shelter in this area.
我们无法解释发生了什么
We have no explanation for what has been happening.
[声音变慢]
[VOICE SLOWS DOWN]
我们在这个地区避难，我们无法解释…
We have taken shelter here. We have no explanation...
我们现在有五个人，我们曾经是一个拥有90万…
We are now five. We were once a nation of 900,000...
[声音加快]
[VOICE SPEEDS UP]
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
有昆虫
There is insect life.
我的三录仪没显示
My tricorder doesn't register it.
这是一个贫瘠的世界，有限的植被，没有动物
This is a barren world, limited vegetation, no animal life.
- 麦考伊呼叫史波克  - 我是史波克
- McCoy to Spock. - Spock here.
我在电脑里找到了一盘磁带，我只能听到嗡嗡声
I found a tape in the computer. All I get is a whine.
马上把它带到舰桥
Bring it to the bridge at once.
连接到生命支持系统的装置
This device attached to the life-support system
产生一种极度的，麻木的寒冷
produces an extreme, numbing cold.
我认为他们正在把企业号变成
I believe they are turning the Enterprise
一个巨大的深度冷冻的
into a gigantic deep-freeze.
该装置有一个防护罩，不允许任何物理接触
The unit has a protective shield which does not allow any physical contact.
我不知道如何摧毁它，但摧毁它势在必行
I don't know how to destroy it, but its destruction is imperative.
迪拉[录音]：装置将被激活
DEELA [ON TAPE]: The unit will be activated.
当他们听到这些时，已经太晚了
By the time they hear this, it will be too late.
乌乎拉，通知其他船员
Uhura, notify the rest of the crew.
我们能切开墙壁，绕过力场获取那个装置吗？
Can we cut through the wall, bypass the force field and get at the unit?
我们无法在我们的级别上应付他们
We cannot cope with them on our level.
以他们的级别呢？
What about on theirs?
这是一个合乎逻辑的建议，在传送室待命
That is a logical suggestion. Stand by in the transporter room.
其他地方没有什么问题，有足够的能量传送下去
There's nothing wrong elsewhere. Sufficient energy for beaming down.
这是唯一的损坏？
This is the only damage?
去找其他人，把他们带到这里来
Go get the others and bring them up here.
迪拉
Deela.
迪拉？
Deela?
雷尔！
Rael!
雷尔，住手
Rael, stop.
现在
Now.
现在，住手
Now, stop it.
- 他伤害了你吗？  - 没有
- Did he damage you? - No.
你真幸运，雷尔
How very fortunate for you, Rael.
不要再做那样的事了，是可鄙的
Don't do anything like that again. It's contemptible.
那就别折磨我了，你知道我的感受
Then don't torment me. You know how I feel.
我不在乎你的感受，我不想知道那个部分
I don't care about your feelings. I don't want to know that aspect.
你无权质疑我的所作所为
You have no right to question what I do.
让我有尊严地喜欢我选择的男人
Allow me the dignity of liking the man I select.
- 传送装置修好了吗？  - 不，我还有更多工作要做
- Is the transporter repaired? - No. I have more work to do.
你不认为你最好去修吗？
Don't you think you'd better do it?
他爱我，我小时候很崇拜他
He loves me. I adored him when I was a child.
我想我仍然爱他
I suppose I still do.
你表现得比他好
You behaved better than he did.
- 但愿如此  - 你说什么？
- I hope so. - What did you say?
我说但愿我表现得不错
I said I hoped I behaved correctly.
现在没有什么困扰你了吗？
And nothing bothers you now?
- 我们为什么在这里？  - 我们的离开被推迟了，记得吗？
- Why are we here? - Our leaving was delayed, remember?
- 你破坏了传送zhu装置ang zhi  - 哦，是的，那是我错了
- You damaged the transport. - Oh, yes. That was wrong of me.
是的，确实如此
Yes, it certainly was.
- 但我们要去斯卡罗斯？  - 你想要去吗？
- But we are going to Scalos? - Do you want to?
- 哦，是的  - 你不担心你的船员吗？
- Oh, yes. - Aren't you worried about your crew?
- 他们会没事的  - 哦
- They'll be all right. - Oh.
- 怎么了？  - 没有什么
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
你已经完全接受了，不是吗？你甚至喜欢它
You've completely accepted the situation, haven't you? You even like it.
- 我表现得不对吗？  - 不
- Am I behaving incorrectly? - No.
我更喜欢以前的你，固执，易怒，有主见，像雷尔
I liked you better before. Stubborn, irritating and independent. Like Rael.
这些都是不受欢迎的品质
Those are undesirable qualities.
也许这就是我喜欢你的原因，因为你和他一样
Maybe that's why I liked you. Because you were like him.
雷尔，你不必担心舰长
Rael, you don't have to worry about the captain.
他适应了
He's made the adjustment.
完成的
Finished.
它最有效地抵消了物质
It counteracts the substance most effectively.
在实验室条件下，但它会在人体中起作用吗？
Under laboratory conditions. But will it work in the human body?
- 我们怎么把它交给舰长？  - 通过喝下斯卡罗斯的水
- And how do we get it to the captain? - By drinking the Scalosian water.
但你不知道这会对你有什么影响
But you don't know what that will do to you.
有点刺激
It is somewhat stimulating.
医生，你似乎走得很慢
You seem to be moving very slowly, Doctor.
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
真有趣
Fascinating.
他消失了
He's gone.
就像康普顿一样
Just like Compton.
我传送其他人下去了
I've beamed the others down.
迪拉[通过无线电]：已经修好了吗？
DEELA [OVER RADIO]: Is it repaired already?
你为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
这本来是一种入侵
It would have been an intrusion.
当你准备好时给我发信号
Signal me when you are ready.
- 你会在哪里？  - 生命支持系统
- Where will you be? - In life-support.
- 我必须激活我们的装置  - 等等
- I have to activate our unit. - Wait.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道
I know.
来吧，舰长，是时候离开你漂亮的船了
Come, Captain. It's time to leave your pretty ship.
装置已启动，迪拉，立刻传送下来
The unit is activated, Deela. Beam down at once.
你的船员会没事的，你自己也是这么说的
You crew will be all right. You said so yourself.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 他离开了，带着武器  - 我准备好了
- He's broken away. He's armed. - I'm ready for him.
你很聪明，舰长，你耍了我
You are very clever, Captain. You tricked me.
我早该知道你永远不会适应
I should have known that you would never adjust.
我们现在应该期待什么？
What shall we expect now?
我们现在可以让你处于假死状态
We could put you in suspended animation for now.
你的存留并不取决于此
Your survival does not depend on that.
不，它不是，你想让我们对你做什么？
No, it doesn't. What do you want us to do with you?
不要把它当作游戏，舰长，我们输了
Don't make a game of it, Captain. We've lost.
如果我把你们送回斯卡罗斯，你们还会玩同样的把戏
If I sent you back to Scalos, you'd play the same trick
对下一艘经过的飞船
on the next passing ship.
不会有其他人了，你会警告他们
There won't be any others. You'll warn them.
你的联邦会隔离整个区域
You will quarantine the entire area.
是的，我想会的
Yes, we will.
我们会死，并以这种方式解决你的问题，还有我们的
And we will die and solve your problem that way. And ours.
你的问题呢，舰长，还有你的瓦肯朋友？
What about your problem, Captain, and your Vulcan friend?
如果你投身于斯卡罗斯的事务
If you will devote yourself exclusively to the concerns of Scalos
我们很乐意留下并照顾企业号
we shall be pleased to take care of the Enterprise.
你仍然可以发现斯卡罗斯的生活非常愉快
You could still find life on Scalos very pleasant.
- 并且非常短暂  - 和这里一样短暂
- And very brief. - It will be just as brief here.
你无法回到你自己的级别
You cannot get back to your own level.
没有答案吗，舰长？
No answer, Captain?
- 我让你这么不高兴吗？  - 哦，不是
- Do I displease you so much? - Oh, no.
我想没有什么比和你在一起更愉快的了
I can think of nothing I'd rather do than stay with you.
除了活着
Except staying alive.
启动
Energize.
再见，舰长
Goodbye, Captain.
你有什么消息？
What have you got?
我们已经合成了一种可能对抗斯卡罗斯的水的反作用剂
We have synthesised a possible counter agent to the Scalosian water.
但是我们没有机会测试它
But we did not have the opportunity to test it.
让我们测试一下
Let's test it.
什么都没有发生
Nothing's happening.
你的动作似乎非常缓慢
You do seem to be moving very slowly.
[慢声]先生…
[SLOW VOICE] Mister...
史波克
Spock.
舰长！你从哪儿来的？
Captain! Where did you come from?
- 不知道从哪儿冒出来的  - 史波克先生也来了吗？
- Out of the nowhere into the here. - Is Mr. Spock coming too?
斯科提
Scotty.
柯克：舰长日志，星历5710.9
KIRK: Captain's log, stardate 5710.9.
史波克先生一直处于加速状态
Mr. Spock has remained in accelerated time
这样他能更快地进行修复
so he might effect repairs more rapidly.
- 有人正在修理每个控制台！  - 电路恢复的速度如此之快！
- Somebody's repairing every console! - They're being recircuited so fast!
我想我们已经找到了史波克先生
I think we've located Mr. Spock.
- 你的电路通畅了吗？  - 是的，长官
- Are your circuits clearing? - Yes, sir.
取消红色警报，打开所有频道
Cancel Red Alert. Open all channels.
舰长呼叫船员，修理工作由史波克先生负责
Captain to crew. Repairs are being effected by Mr. Spock.
该船即将恢复正常运行
The ship will resume normal operations almost immediately.
史波克先生，我向你的维修工作和你致敬
Mr. Spock. My compliments to your repair work and yourself.
谢谢，舰长，我发现这是一种加速体验
Thank you, Captain. I found it an accelerating experience.
是的…
Yes...
没有故障了吧？
No malfunctions anywhere?
上尉
Lieutenant.
抱歉，我不小心碰到了磁带按钮，我会把它取下来
I'm sorry. I touched the tape button accidentally. I'll take it off.
那是…没有故障
That's... no malfunction.
没有，长官
No, sir.
再见，迪拉，
Goodbye, Deela.